This is standard relaxation therapy for the low back.
A lot of people have low back problems and the low back is an area that often times doesn't get as much attention as it deserves.
As always start by assessing the area that you are working on with just some gentle effleurage.
Get an idea of the tonal quality of the muscles.
Low back is easily divided on either side.
And it's actually going to work over to the side and into the tops of the hip bones.
All those muscles are interconnected.
This is an area that once you've warmed it up with some good effleurage you can get deep effleurage going and then get into the even deeper pretissage.
The kneading motion.
Working around to the hip bone and even on to the very top edge of the gluteal muscles.
Again be careful going across the base of the spine and be careful going across the sacrum as well.
You got bone there with not much else then skin on top of it.
So if you go too deep there it can cause pain and even bruising.
Again good deep motion, you can get alternate deep strokes going.
It helps to warm things up.
That's going to be standard relaxation therapy for the low back.